<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Vision to Results</string>
    <string name="app_loading">App Loading&#8230;</string>
    <string name="set_direction">Set Direction</string>
    <string name="enable_execute">Enable &amp; Execute</string>
    <string name="engage_excite">Engage &amp; Excite</string>
    <string name="sustain_momentum">Sustain Momentum</string>

    <string name="push_message">Your daily inspire me tip has arrived</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="inspire_me">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Inspire &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Me &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="tips_collection">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Tips &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Collection &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="my_favourites">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>My &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Favourites &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="my_settings">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>My &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Settings &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="share_app">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Share &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>App &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="vtr_ebook">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>VTR &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>E-Book &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="about_teletech">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>About &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Teletech &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="about_vtr">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>About &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>VTR &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="contact_us">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Contact &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Us &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="faqs">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>FAQs&lt;/font></string>
    <string name="suggest_tip">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Suggest a  &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'>Tip &lt;/font></string>
    <string name="call_me_back_header">&lt;font color=\'#ee2b7b\'>Call &lt;/font> &lt;font color=\'#60605b\'> me back&lt;/font></string>
    <string name="contact_us_button">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="call_us">Call Us</string>
    <string name="email_us">Email Us</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="call_me_back">Call me back</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="contactus_content">Interested in finding out more about our Vision to Results methodology? Contact Us</string>
    <string name="from_time">From Time</string>
    <string name="to_time">To Time</string>
    <string name="vtr_e_book">VTR E-Book</string>
    <string name="vision_to_results">Vision To Results</string>
    <string name="visit_website">Visit Website</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="twitter_handler">Twitter Handle</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="tip">Tip</string>
    <string name="preferred_time">Preferred Time</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="share_tip">Share Tip</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection.</string>
    <string name="no_favourite">No Favourites</string>
    <string name="no_favourite_message">You can save your favourite tips by clicking the star icon on the back of tip cards.</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for_sharing_app">Thank you for sharing Vision to Results.</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for_suggestion">Thank you for your suggestion.</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank You</string>
    <string name="ebook_email_submission">We have received your email and will let you know when the book is released.</string>
    <string name="call_me_back_submission">We have received your details and one of our team members will be in touch shortly.</string>
    <string name="your_settings_updated">Your settings have been updated.</string>
    <string name="tip_added_favourite">This Tip has been added to your favourites.</string>
    <string name="tip_remove_favourite">This Tip has been removed from your favourites.</string>
    <string name="app_not_installed">App Not Installed</string>
    <string name="no_such_app_found_for_sharing">No such app is available for sharing.</string>
    <string name="share_via_email">Share via Email</string>
    <string name="value_required">Value Required</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Invalid Email</string>
    <string name="share_via_sms">Share via SMS</string>
    <string name="notification_on">Notification ON</string>
    <string name="notification_off">Notification OFF</string>
    <string name="suggest_tip_content">Have you got a great VTR Tip that you would like to share with us?</string>
    <string name="share_app_content_one">You can share the Vision to Results App with your friends and colleagues.</string>
    <string name="share_app_content_second">Hi,\nI am using a new App called Vision to Results by Teletech and thought you might find it useful.</string>
    <string name="callmeback_content">Please enter your details below and a member of staff will get call you at your preferred time. </string>
    <string name="vtrebook_content_first">including JP Morgan,Johnson &amp; Johnson, Macquarie Bank, Kraft  Foods, UBS, Carlsberg and Rabobank.</string>
    <string name="vtrebook_content_second">DRIVERS - A PARABLE OF RESULTS\n\nby Terry Reynolds and Glenn Price\nTeleTech Consulting\nCopyright 2014 TeleTech Holdings Inc.</string>
    <string name="vtrebook_content_third">\n\nChapter One - Vision\n\nScott Boylan measured his client’s moods as much with his ears as his eyes. The client didn’t need to say a word. Scott just needed the first five seconds after they opened the car door. “They’re giving themselves away from the moment they grab the handle,” he told his younger drivers. “By the time they’ve sat down and put on their seat belts, I know whether they’re happy about where they’ve been, or glad to be going where they’re going!”\n\nThen again, you didn’t always need three decades’ experience to read a mood. This morning’s first passenger snatched at the door and sank into the seat as if he’d like to shut the world out for good. Those moods, Scott knew, called for less - not more.\n\n“Straight to the office, Mr Dalton?”\n\n“Just drive, Scott,” said the man in the tailored suit, pushing a hand through rain-wet hair.\n\nInfinity Investments was Scott’s biggest account. He and three of his five drivers spent most of their time driving the staff of Infinity from home to the office, from the office to meetings, and home again, but often via a dinner or function. He knew where they all lived, where they went on holiday and when they went on holiday because it was Scott or one of his drivers who took them to the airport. Scott knew which children played tennis and which ones loved to ski. To the children he was a happy sight - the beginning of holiday adventures. To his clients he was sometimes the first face they saw on a bad day. Today was obviously one of those days for Alex Dalton.\n\nScott checked the road over his shoulder and slid the town car away from the kerb and into the drizzle. If the CEO of Infinity Investments wanted to put off going into the office with a circuit of the city, Scott wasn’t going to ask questions.\n\nIn the back, the CEO followed the raindrops on the window, as the motion of the car pushed the water upwards and sideways in random patterns. Scott glanced at him in the rearview mirror. When you added up all the journeys over the years, the two men had talked for hours. They’d discussed the news of the day, the economy and their children. Their greatest passion was saved for their frustrations with the sports teams each man had inexplicably continued to support, despite all the let downs and heartbreak they had brought him over the years.\n\nThe lights of the cars in front drew red tracks in the wet road as Scott kept a steady pace in the inside lane. Five minutes passed before the CEO broke the silence.\n\n“I’m sorry, Scott,” he said meeting the driver’s eyes in the mirror. “It’s been a hell of a week. A hell of a month actually, but that’s no excuse.”\n\n“That’s all right, Mr Dalton. You know I’m happy to drive you wherever you want to go or nowhere at all - even on a morning like this one.”\n\n“It’s just nice to be moving, frankly,” the CEO said turning back to look through misted window.\n\n“It’s been a tough few years for all businesses, Mr Dalton,” said Scott.\n\n“You know that feeling when your car isn’t moving but the cars next to you are?”\n\n“When you feel like you’re going backwards?”\n\n“Exactly. You feel like you’re moving but you’re just standing still. And standing still in business is dangerous. If you’re standing still and your competitors are going forwards, you might as well be going backwards.”\n\n“It sounds like a difficult time.”\n\n“I’m sorry again, Scott. I don’t mean to be as miserable as this weather or to talk in riddles. But you read the papers… like you say, ‘it’s a tough market’. I’ve been there before, but now everything seems to change every 10 minutes. I’ve got managers telling me all the time their teams are asking ‘where we’re going?’ and ‘what we’re going to do?’. At the same time, I’ve got the board on my back demanding results. I’m not sure they read the papers. It’s always the same. Numbers. Quarterly targets. Half-yearly targets. I don’t know where they think these numbers are going to come from. It’s nothing but guesswork! Half my competitors are going one way and the rest are  going the other.”\n\n“Infinity’s a big company, Mr Dalton,” said Scott. “Surely it’s not just you? You must have some help?”\n\n“My team seems to have more opinions than there are people. Everyone’s looking for answers, and I don’t have anything more than questions myself. Some days, it feels like it’s taking everything I’ve got just to stop us actually going backwards instead of just feeling that we are. If standing still is taking all my energy, I don’t know where I’m going to find the drive to get us somewhere else!”\n\n“Have I ever told you how I choose a new driver, Mr Dalton?”\n\nAlex raised an eyebrow and turned away from the blurry shapes through the window. “I don’t think you have,” he said.\n\n“The interview’s probably not what you’d expect,” said Scott. “It’s certainly not what they are expecting.”\n\nScott’s business had grown steadily from one car and one driver - Scott himself, to three cars and five drivers working in shifts. Scott’s drivers liked working for him and as a result driver turnover was low. Occasionally, however, he’d had to interview replacement drivers and new drivers for his expanded fleet.\n\n“I have to be careful,” he said. “My whole business is in their hands every time they pick someone up. I can’t be there when they’re on a job. If they don’t give our clients the sort of service I want to be known for, they could lose me that client for good, and I might not even know why. People often prefer to say nothing when they don’t like something and just find another company. So I’m looking for more than a clean driving licence and the right number of years of experience. I’m hiring a person, not a checklist of qualifications or milestones.”\n\n“A literal collection of milestones in your case, of course,” said Alex.\n\n“And those milestones are passed in the driving seat. But I’m giving the person I hire responsibility for growing my business. I need them to sell the experience. That’s why my drivers all start in the back seat.”\n\nScott explained that after going through the formalities in his office, he’d take the potential new driver outside to the firm’s newest town car and tell them it was time to go for a drive. Invariably, the driver would start for the driver’s door before they noticed Scott holding open the rear door for them. “Where to?” he’d ask.\n\n“The thing is, Mr Dalton, there’s more to driving than just driving. You can tell a great deal about a person from where they want to go. Sure, it takes some coaxing. They’re drivers, they’re used to doing the asking. But once they realise that I’m serious, they give it some thought. They have to. It’s not a metaphor, we can’t go anywhere until they’ve picked a destination, and that tells me a lot about them.”\n\n“What can you tell about someone from that?” said Alex sitting up in his seat.\n\n“Some of them want to drive round the sights or head for the upmarket parts of town, seeing it all from the backseat of a smart car for a change. They tend to be the ambitious ones. Others want to drive past their kids’ schools or their mum’s house. They’re the ones who work for their families. We’re all doing the same job, but we’re not doing it for the same reasons.”\n\nWhile Scott chauffeured a potential driver, he told Alex, he would explain to them his business philosophy.\n\n“The speech is always the same. I tell them ‘driving’s our business, but getting the client from A to B is only the start. If you want repeat business, you need to pay attention to the route you’re going to take to get them there’. Sometimes it’s easy, but sometimes you get the best result from a less obvious route. The drivers who get and keep the sort of clients I’m aiming for, are the ones who know driving is just the start.\n\n“But who am I telling, Mr Dalton? You’ve been with me since it was just me driving. There are thousands of drivers for hire in this city. Obviously, they all know how to drive and for the most part, they all know how to get from A to B. If my business were just about being able to drive a car round the city, it  would be no different from a hundred other companies, maybe a thousand. My business grew because I knew being successful in this game wasn’t going to be about being a better driver, it was going to be about giving clients a better journey.\n\nPeople talk about their drivers all the time. Mostly, they talk about them to complain – ‘too chatty, too opinionated, too heavy on the brakes’. I wanted to build a company people talked about because we got everything ‘just right’. We’re there on time, we’ve already thought about the fastest route, and we’ll let you know if we’re expecting any problems on the way. We talk - if the client would like to chat, and we keep quiet if it looks like they want time to think. And people do talk about us. Almost all my business comes from people recommending us - and it’s not our driving they’re talking about, it’s the journey!”\n\nScott heard the rustle of the CEO’s suit on the leather upholstery as Alex shifted forward in the back seat.\n\n“Scott, you’re a wise man,” Alex said touching him on the shoulder. “I’m ready to go to the office now, but if you’ll excuse me, I’ve got a call to make first.”\n\nAlex pulled his phone from his pocket. “Mia,” he said to his assistant. “I want the leadership team in the conference room as soon as they come in!!”\n\nIt seemed to Heather Durrant that the boss almost bounced into the conference room. There was more length in his stride than she’d seen for a long time. She chose to take it as a good sign. In other jobs, unexpected calls to meeting rooms first thing in the morning hadn’t signalled good things, especially for the head of HR. Infinity had been sailing through some choppy waters, but this morning the captain of the ship didn’t seem too worried. He seemed, could she be right, excited?\n\nAlex caught the eye of each of his team as he walked the length of the conference table. Nearest the door, with her back to the conference room’s impressive view of the city, sat Heather, a tall waxed paper cup of coffee on the table in front of her. Heather was respected by all for her ability to balance the needs of the business, with the needs of the individuals who worked for it. Next to her was Kathryn Chivers, a Hermes scarf adding a splash of colour to her conservative suit. The communications director was the oldest of the group, and was trusted for her counsel and discretion. Michael Stockley, Infinity’s sales director, sat a few seats apart, looking up from his iPhone to catch Alex’s eye as he passed. The newest member of the team, his enthusiasm for meeting his sales targets led to the occasional tense conversations with anyone he felt was getting in the sales team’s way.\n\nThey rippled forward as Alex passed and he knew he had their attention.\n\nArriving at the whiteboard, Alex turned his back to the room and began to write. He could sense the three of them craning their necks behind him, straining for the first inkling of what the impromptu meeting was about. He heard Michael put his phone down on the table. When Alex turned around there were three questions behind him on the board: ‘Who are we? Why are we here? What do we believe?’\n\nAlex looked down the table, smiled and spread his hands expectantly. For a moment, all they could hear was the sound of the rain tapping on the windows.\n\nAlex looked at each of them, saying nothing.\n\n“Well, my name’s Michael,” said Michael eventually. “I’m here to make money, and I believe I should be out there now making some calls to do it.” The joke fell flat.\n\n“That’s good, Michael,” said Alex,  “No,I mean it. They’re important questions and I don’t think we’ve answered them or, if we have, we’ve never said it out loud. ‘What is this business for?’ ‘What is our purpose?’ And ‘why are we the right ones to be doing it’, if we are?”\n\n“Do you mean ‘if we are doing it?’ or ‘if we’re the right ones to be doing it?” said Kathryn.\n\n“Either. Both,” said Alex. “And, if we are the right ones to be doing it, ‘what do we need to change to do it right?’ At the same time, if someone told us we had to make changes, what would we say we were definitely keeping because it was truly working? What is it that we believe in as a group that has got us this far… and might get us further?”\n\n“I find these sort of existential questions are generally best left to HR,” said Kathryn swivelling her chair to face Heather.\n\n“Sure. Push the big questions to HR. We can handle it,” said Heather, turning her head from Kathryn. She unclenched her jaw as she looked back at Alex. “Maybe you need to help us out a bit, Alex. It’s still early and I’d have ordered a Expresso Grande if I knew I’d be tackling the meaning of life today.” She took a sip of her coffee, looking over the rim at the CEO.\n\n“Fair enough, Heather,” said Alex, pulling out the chair at the head of the table and sitting down. “The questions are big, but not quite that big. If we get onto the meaning of life, I’ll get Mia to order you a bigger coffee. For now, I’m talking about us, Infinity. It was a nice swerve by Kathryn. But, maybe she’s right. You’re at least in the best position to answer the ‘who’ questions. You know more about our people than anyone. If we look at the company, what sort of team have we built? Do you think it’s the right sort? Are we all like Michael, mainly for the money? Or is there something else that brings us here?”\n\n“Not to state the obvious, and loathe as I am to agree with Michael under most circumstances, but the pay is good and Infinity has pedigree,” said Heather. “There is a money element, and we’re not a bad name to have on a resume.”\n\n“We’re in financial services. Of course it’s about the money!” said Michael. “We’re a good name to have on your resume when you go for another job and when you find one that’s offering more money. If you’re in this business of all businesses, and it doesn’t come back to money for you, you’re in the wrong place my friends.”\n\n“Sure, but we don’t pay more than anyone else and there are plenty of good names out there,” said Alex. “Do people just end up here because it’s where the chips fell? Or, as Michael says, because it’s a rung on the ladder to the next place?”\n\nThere was a silence in the room.\n\n“I know why I came, if that helps,” said Kathryn, breaking the tension. “You know where I was before and you know their reputation. When you work there, work is what you do. It was like Eisner said at Disney, ‘If you don’t come in on Saturday, don’t bother coming in on Sunday.’ Work was all you’d do because you didn’t have time for anything else. I heard Infinity was different, and I wanted to try it.”\n\n“And what did you find?” asked Alex.\n\n“I found I stayed,” said Kathryn. “I liked it. I still like it. It amazed me that the quality of the work was just as good and so were the results. I wish I’d come sooner.”\n\n“That’s true of a lot of our people,” said Heather nodding. “They’ve done the other thing. They thought working 70 or 80-hour weeks was the way to get ahead. If you left before midnight and were back after seven, you weren’t serious - that kind of thing. They come here when they want to see if there really can be more to life than work, without giving up doing what they love to do.”\n\n“Infinity. Where tree-huggers look after your investments,” said Michael, “but only until 5 pm! No wonder we’re in trouble.” He reached for his phone again.\n\n“You don’t need to be a tree-hugger to want to have more to life than a never-empty inbox,” said Kathryn pointing at the phone. “Believe it or not there are people who think it’s possible to do a great job and still have horizons wider than a couple of 27-inch monitors, the bar across the road, and a home they never see in the daylight.”\n\n“What’s wrong with the bar across the road?” said Michael looking genuinely puzzled. “It’s the best beer in the city!”\n\n“I think that’s right Kate,” said Heather ignoring him. “We don’t put it in the job ads, but people ask me about it when they come for an interview. They’ve heard we’re not the same.”\n\n“And you, Michael?” said Alex. “Seriously, is that why you’re here? For the money and the proximity of a decent microbrewery?”\n\n“Are you asking me if there’s more to life than selling investments, Alex? Because you know there isn’t. Not for me.”\n\n“Come on, Michael,” said Alex smiling. “We know you’re a master of the universe, but even you aren’t the Wolf of Wall Street.”\n\n“All right, you got me. I did come here because I’d had enough. I love my work, but there’s more to me than that. One day I’ll show you my watercolours, Kathryn.” The laughter in the room lightened the mood. “You all know I’ve got a family, and of course I know I’ve got a family but, if I’m being honest, I didn’t properly realise that for a long time. I missed a few too many school plays before I got the message. I do love what I do, but after a while I wanted to see if it was possible to have more. I would not have said this before, but that’s why I called when I heard you were looking for a new sales director.”\n\n“Now, that’s enough gushing from me. What do you mean ‘what’s our purpose? Now I’ve poured my heart out, I don’t want to come over all Jordan Belfort again, but it’s not complicated is it? We’re here to sell investments.”\n\n“Family man status aside, you’re not what you’d call a layered person are you Michael?” said Kathryn tilting her head and looking at him quizzically.\n\n“I was reminded on the way to work this morning that it’s a mistake to take a business on face value. What we do has to be more than just selling investments,” said Alex. “Hotels don’t just sell rooms with beds. They sell experiences. You choose one over the other for a number of reasons, but part of it is the experience, and part of it is what they value. This one is about ‘exceptional service’. That one is about ‘comfort’ or ‘efficiency’ or ‘convenience’ or ‘expense’ or whatever. Boiling it down, the way you are Michael, there’s nothing to choose between one hotel or another. At their most basic, they’re all collections of rooms with beds, like we’re all just firms with investment products.”\n\n“You’re right,” said Heather. “If you said ‘Hyatt’ to me or ‘Hilton’, ‘The Plaza’ or ‘The Savoy’, I’d instantly have an image in my mind. I have an idea what they stand for, and why I’d choose one not the other.”\n\n“Assuming you had the money to make a choice,” said Michael.\n\n“Yes Michael, money is part of it,” said Kathryn. “No one is disagreeing with you about that. But Alex is right, we’ve let ourselves become indistinguishable from everyone else. We’ve forgotten why we’re in this business and who we’re in it for. And if we’re the same as everyone else, then there’s no point in our being here.”\n\n“And if we can’t see any point in our being here ourselves, why on earth would a client choose us?” added Heather.\n\n“Look. I do take your point. I’m not a complete idiot. I just think sometimes you forget what makes everything else possible around here,” said Michael. “If we think we’re attracting people to work here because we’re so different, why don’t we offer clients the same thing we offer our own people?”\n\n“What do you mean?” said Alex.\n\n“Offer them a life-changing investment.”\n\n“You mean only offer them high-risk investments?” asked Kathryn.\n\n“No, not high-risk, not necessarily,” said Michael. “A big return would change some people’s lives, but so would a big loss. An investment that brought financial peace-of-mind would change some people’s lives. For others, it would be knowing that they could put a child through university. What changes one person’s life, might be different from what changes another’s.”\n\n“So the thing would be getting to know why the client is investing, and putting them into investments that could really get them there…” said Kathryn nodding her head slowly. “I like it!”\n\n“Infinity. Life-changing investments… It works!” said Alex.\n\n“It works for clients, and it works for everyone on the team,” said Heather. “We make an investment in the people who work here. We pay what the rest of the industry pays, but we trust people to do great work in a reasonable time. We don’t treat them like we pay by the hour, and we’ve bought all their hours.”\n\n“So what would you say were the beliefs that’s got us this far  - even if we didn’t realise those beliefs were what was holding us together?” said Alex.\n\n“A belief in people,” said Heather leaning forward. “We believe that people don’t need to be pushed to the limit to do a good job. In fact, they probably don’t do a good job if they’re always operating at their limit.”\n\n“Also we believe we do it differently,” said Kathryn. “We believe it is possible to stand out and be different in this industry, that we’re not all the same.”\n\n“And we believe there’s a value to that difference,” said Michael.\n\n“I believe we’ve fitted a missing piece!” said Alex putting his palms together and looking at each of them. “We know why we’re here, we know why people want to work here, and we know why our customers are going to join us. Because we’re not just about investments."\n\nIt’s been a good morning’s work, and I would give you the rest of the day off, but we’ve got lives to change. And now we know where Infinity’s going, we need to talk about how we’re going to get there. I’m not unrealistic. I know you’ve all got projects on and full schedules, so I’m not going to ask you to clear your diaries and stay here to talk about it today.”\n\n“That’s a relief,” said Michael. “I’ve got four client meetings today.”\n\n“Like I say, I’m not unrealistic,” said Alex. “So we’ll say tomorrow morning at the same time.\n\nI shall look forward to your ideas.”</string>
    <string name="vtrebook_content_four">\nIf you would like to be notified when the VTR book is released, please enter your email below.</string>
    <string name="mysetting_content">Vision to Results will send you a new \'Inspire Me\' card each day at 8.00am. You can turn this on or off using the switch below.</string>
    <string name="about_content">Our company was founded more than three decades ago on one guiding principle: Customer relationships build on trust and simplicity deliver lasting value for everyone. In other words, happy customers equal happy companies. </string>
    <string name="about_vtr_content">Here will be some sentences about \'Visions to Results\'. \n\nWe can choose which image to use in the top area of this screen during the development stage of the project.</string>

    <string-array name="slidemenu">
        <item>@string/inspire_me</item>
        <item>@string/tips_collection</item>
        <item>@string/my_favourites</item>
        <item>@string/my_settings</item>
        <item>@string/about_vtr</item>
        <item>@string/about_teletech</item>
        <item>@string/contact_us</item>
        <item>@string/share_app</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="faq_question">
        <item>How do I view a new Inspire Me Card?</item>
        <item>Can I share the Tip Cards?</item>
        <item>How do I save a card to my favourites?</item>
        <item>What is the daily notification?</item>
        <item>How can I share this App with my friends?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="faq_answer">
        <item>You can view a new random Inspire Me Tip Card by shaking your device while in the ‘Inspire Me’ section.</item>
        <item>Yes, simply flip the Tip Card over by swiping the screen and then click the share button at the bottom of the card.</item>
        <item>You can save a card by clicking on the star icon.</item>
        <item>You can set an alarm for 8am each day to remind you to view a new Inspire Me Card. You can switch this on or off from within your settings area.</item>
        <item>You can share Vision to Results by visiting the ‘Share App’ area and then choosing to share with your contacts either via email or SMS.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
